

Elizabeth Mackin ui designer & developer

I am a seasoned graphic desiger with a great passion for design and technology. I strive to combine the two to create beautiful and meaningful user experiences. I am commited to staying current and expanding my knowledge by constantly exploring new ideas and technologies. If you would like to learn more about me or my work, please use any of the below links to get in touch, or visit my website, elizabethmackin.ca

- 905 235 1606 / 289 231 7801
- beth@elizabethmackin.ca
- in linkedin.com/in/emackin
- github.com/bmackin
- twitter.com/bethmackin1

EXPERIENCE

June 2012 - Present
 GRAPHIC DESIGNER /

Homes & Land Magazine, York, Durham, Peterborough & Kawarthas Regions

Design and layout of ads and editorial content Assisted with rebranding strategy

August 2012 - Present
 CREATIVE DIRECTOR /

North Bear Design, Toronto, ON

Creation of brand and marketing strategy Creative direction of projects

• Dec 2011 - June 2012
CREATIVE DESIGNER /
SNAP Newspapers, Newmarket ON

Ad design and layout of editorial content for 3 issues per month

Nov 2007 - Sept 2011
 AD BUILDER/PRE PRESS TECH /

The Record, Kitchener ON

Design and layout of ads for newspaper, special section, and Metroland media owned magazines

April 2003 - Sept 2007ART DIRECTOR /

Federal Impressions Inc., Cambridge ON Creative and quality control of all projects, in-house and outsourced

July 1998 - March 2003
 Studio B Productions, Vancouver BC
 STUDIO MANAGER /

Managed creative and administrative staff Organization of events, parties and PR opportunities

GRAPHIC DESIGNER /

Design of ads, pitch packs, newsletters and press kits for show promotions

MEDIA & PRODUCTION CO-ORDINATOR /

Assisted marketing in developing and running promotional campaigns for in-development properties

Production assistant, "Gahan Wilson's 'The Kid'" (animated mini series, 2001, Nelvana / TMN co-production)

EDUCATION

Sept 1991 - May 1992 **Art Fundamentals Sheridan College,** Oakville, ON Sept 1992 - May 1995 **Graphic Design Sheridan College**, Oakville, ON Jan 2014 - March 2014 **Web Development** *Bitmaker Labs*, Toronto, ON

SKILLS

Professional

- Editorial, Advertising & Web Design
- · Logo Design
- Branding
- Typography
- Offset & Digital Printing Technologies
- Object Oriented
 Programming
- Project Management

Languages / Tools

- HTML5
- · CSS3
- Javascript / jQuery
- · Ruby/Rails
- PostgreSQL
- Git/GitHub
- Sublime
- WordPress
- Adobe CC
- Quark Express

Personal

- Art & Design
- Sailing
- Running
- Music
- Equestrian Riding
- Cooking